The autumn leaves are beautiful.
We're well into fall, aren't we, Desumi-san?
We sure are, Fudo.
I just remembered, Fudo.
Take this.
Kokutei Festival
Kokutei High School School Festival
"Kokutei Festival"?
Your school festival?
Yeah, are you free for it next weekend?
My class is doing a maid café.
Desumi-san... dressed as a maid?!
I would give my life to attend!
Hooray!
But make sure you come on Sunday,
the festival's last day.
There's a legend at Kokutei High School.
For the finale of the final
day of the Kokutei Festival,
the staff makes a crescent-shaped
sculpture available for one hour only.
It's called the "Kokutei Moon."
The Kokutei Moon is a popular spot for
couples to take pictures together.
And it's said that those who do
become invincible couples,
bound in love for eternity.
Well? Isn't that interesting?!
What a clever idea!
I already consider us an invincible couple,
but I wouldn't object to having
a little supernatural backing!
But a school festival will
surely be extremely crowded...
Yes, we must be certain we aren't seen.
This will no doubt be our
toughest mission yet!
Bring it on, I say!
Let's do it, Desumi-san!
Yes, Fudo!
Let's become an invincible couple!
Kokutei High School Handball Club
Kokutei High School Naginata Club
Kokutei High School Basketball Club
Kokutei Festival
Episode 10     Atop the Kokutei Moon
Cotton Candy
Hey, isn't that...
No way!
I don't believe it!
What's he doing here?!
Yeah!
It's Hayato-kun, the hero!
That's right, I'm finally here!
The cerulean gem of Gelato 5,
Hayato Ojino is in the building!
And the crimson brick, Fudo, is here too!
Fudo-kun!
Hot stuff!
Why are you doing this, Hayato?
Silence, traitor.
This is your punishment for trying to
attend this blissful event
without inviting me along!
Can you at least try to be subtle about it?
Nope!
Look at me!
I want all girls, front and center!
Don't be shy, or you'll regret it!
Two! Change Gelat—
Now, which version is your preferred flavor?
Two! Change—
Go!
Two! Change Gelato!
Ouch!
Hey! Where are you going, Fudo?!
What?
Where's Fudo-kun?
There he is!
Fudo-kun!
Not good!
I'll come to see you at your shop
We're in classroom 2-B
I'm sorry, Desumi-san
Things have gotten a little complicated
Have a good day, master!
A little complicated?
Hey, Desumi!
What's up? You seem distracted.
N-No, I'm fine!
Help us make parfaits!
S-Sure, on my way!
H-Hojo-san?!
"Things have gotten a little complicated"?
What's all this now, Desucchi?
Meeting up with your boyfriend?
O-Of course not...
Yeah?
No real plans, then?
In that case...
Wanna go to the Kokutei Moon with me?
C'mon. We'd be an invincible couple!
Well? Well?
Wait, I...
Well?
I don't know what you're talking about!
Wait for me, Desucchi!
Hey, wanna go to the Kokutei Moon?
Why would we need to?
We're already deeply in love, honey.
Yeah...
No one can ever tear us a—
Discipline Officer
Threatening
Who the heck are you?!
The discipline officer!
The purpose of school festivals is
to promote a spirit of community!
Not to get all lovey-dovey!
You hear me?
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Goodness me.
Are you jealous because
you're all alone, Kiki-san?
What was that, Kyoko?!
I'm not jealous!
Lapses in discipline lead
to lapses in morality!
I won't leave a single couple standing!
Scary.
Then I'd better get away before
you try to take us down.
What?
Right, Bear-sama?
Plush
Are you crazy or something?!
And why the hell isn't the sight of a
bear in school causing a mass panic?
Look at that bear costume!
Awesome quality!
Nice! Must be pretty hot in that thing!
Now I bid you good day, Kiki-san.
Keep the violence to a minimum, would you?
Death to all couples!
Haunted House
I'm sorry, Desumi-san
Things have gotten a little complicated
Let's meet up
in the haunted house
Classroom 3-A
I think I finally lost her...
Desumi-san!
Fudo!
Your unprecedented cuteness revolutionizes
the concept of the maid!
The word "cute" hardly
seems sufficient anymore!
Thoughtful
This is no time for that!
Let's hide back there!
I'm sorry, Fudo.
This has all been such a mess.
No, a glance at you in your maid
outfit makes anything worthwhile.
R-Really? I'm glad...
But you're embarrassing me again!
Oh, that's right...
Look, Fudo.
These are the sweets we serve
in our class's maid café.
W-Welcome home, master!
I might be the luckiest master
in all of human history!
Oh, you!
They're delicious.
I'm glad to hear it.
But... it really might be impossible
for us to be alone together
at the school festival, Fudo.
No, I believe we can overcome any
trial the world throws at us!
We must arrive at it no matter what...
Our shared Kokutei Moon!
Fudo...
Yes, you're right.
I should have confidence in us.
I feel bad for leaving my class in the lurch,
but let's wait here until the finale—
Illicit heterosexual relations detected!
I'm going to crush you!
Tell me your year and class number!
Run!
Desumi-san!
Fudo!
Let's meet up again later!
I think I lost her.
Don't be so cold, Desucchi.
You promised you'd go to
the Kokutei Moon with me!
I don't think I did!
UMA Study Group
Famous UMA-yaki
This is gonna be fun!
The couples have begun their exodus.
We have very little time left!
Where have you been, Fudo?
You promised you'd serve
as my horse all day long!
I never made any such promise!
There he is!
Hayato!
Fudo-kun!
Right here!
Sorry to keep you waiting, all!
Attention, Kokutei Festival goers!
The time has arrived!
It's the shining jewel of the
Kokutei festival finale...
the Kokutei Moon!
It will be available for one hour only!
All couples, please gather
around the front entrance!
Love After World Domination!
Desucchi!
You can't get away from me, Desucchi!
H-Hojo-san! You're really
athletic, aren't you?!
Nurse's Office
Just give in already, Desucchi!
My, my. Magahara-san...
I need your h-help, Blood Princess!
None of that, now, Reaper-chan.
You're not supposed to
call me that at school.
Gekko Princess Series
Blood Princess
Kira Sanzugawa
S-Sorry about that, Sanzugawa-sensei!
But I have some urgent business to attend to!
Could you hold off the girl on the
other side of this door for me?
I can't seem to get her to leave me alone!
That's no good, now.
Bosslar-chan would be furious if he
caught me using my powers at school!
Please! I'm begging you!
I'm afraid not.
I-I'll give you a Super Bosslar-kun Doll!
squee♥
Allow me to explain!
Blood Princess is in love
with Supreme Ruler Bosslar!
Well, perhaps just this once!
Thanks!
You're not going anywhere, Hojo-san.
Ugh, Blood Princess...
This sucks.
Why don't you stick around and
have a nice, long talk with me?
Stop me, if you think you can.
Bad girl.
Nurse's Office Announcements
Gracious. You're awfully strong, aren't you?
That's 'cause I'm also part
of the Princess Series!
An explosion?
Some kind of event?
That bought me a little time, at least.
So cute!
Isn't that Red and Blue?
What are they doing?
Red?
Good boy!
spank
Run, run!
Wa ha ha ha
spank
What in the world is happening there?
Desumi-san!
Hot stuff!
Fudo?
Hey, Desumi.
Kiki?
You got nothing better to do, right?
Come help me track down couples.
She didn't realize that was
me in the haunted house?
That's a relief.
A-Actually, I do have a few plans...
But we've reached the finale.
What plans could you have?
Wait a minute...
You did mention you were interested
in romance that one time.
Don't tell me you've got a boyfriend, too!
Wait! Calm down!
Shiver...
Th-This chilling aura...
We meet again.
H-He's...
We meet again. We meet again. We meet again.
We meet again. We meet again...
Haven't seen you since the beach!
Hayato!
Fudo!
Now's our chance!
R-Right!
We're running out of time!
I know that.
But they all recognize you...
And Princess Series members
are all around us.
Kokutei Festival
Just five minutes left with the Kokutei Moon!
To break through the crowd and sit
there without anyone seeing us...
I'm out of ideas!
Who in the world are you?
I thought you were Bear-sama!
Hang on! You're the one who grabbed on to me!
What are you trying to pull with
this extremely detailed costume?!
I just really like bears, okay?!
Then where is the real Bear-sama?!
How should I know?!
Oh, for pity's sake!
Cosplay makes everything so confusing!
Fudo! We still have a chance!
We can't give up yet!
Desumi-san?
We'll take one more couple
before closing up shop!
Kokutei Festival
A-Are you sure we can do it?
Yes, I know that we can.
There's nothing we can't do!
Right?
Indeed.
You're right,
Desumi-san!
Freezing Change!
Welcome Evil! Punish Good!
One! Change Gelato!
Reaper Change!
Let's go, Desumi-san!
Yes, Fudo!
Just one couple left?
Hey, look at that!
That's so cool!
Awesome taste!
Amazing quality, too!
It's pretty fanfic, though.
Totally.
Red Gelato and Reaper Princess, getting along?
When you and I work together,
there is nothing that we cannot achieve.
Yes, because we are an invincible couple.
Perhaps the day when we can see
each other with heads held high
isn't so far away after all, Fudo.
Yes indeed, Desumi-san.
And until that day comes, I'm going
to enjoy having this little secret!
Yes.
Okay! I'm taking the picture!
Hey, did you hear?
Culverin Bear and Steel-chan are dating!
Oh hang on, is that for real?
I totally had a feeling, though!
I hear they were together at the
high school culture festival.
Young love goals!
A culture festival date
is total young love goals!
Right?
But inter-company romance
is against the rules.
So actually going through with it
seems a little inappropriate.
But that's what makes it frickin' sweet!
Hey, hey...
If you were gonna date someone,
who'd you go for? Matchlock Eagle?
Oh, no!
He's far too self-aggrandizing.
Then what about Railgun Lion?
I don't think so...
I can't handle those "ora-ora" types.
Hard same!
Gatling Wolf?
He's too neurotic and fastidious.
I don't think I could ever date him.
A good man is hard to find, isn't he?
Yeah, and it's so crazy!
I can't believe Steel's into Culverin Bear!
She is still young, though.
Maybe she's confused huggability
for something else.
Doubt you'll see any other member of the
Princess Series doing the romance thing!
What about Reaper-chan?
Reaper, huh? Yeah, nah!
You think?
Oh, totes nah!
Yeah, you're right.
I'm back!
Have you been a good girl?
My mistress had another good day, I suppose.
Ready for my hot bath!
Because of that goon of a man, I suppose.
Not that I like to admit it.
But if my mistress is happy,
I suppose I'll allow it.
What is justice? What is peace?
Like hot-burning ice, they break
through the chaos of the age!
Their name, Freezing Sentai Gelato 5!
Tune in next week!
Next time, Episode 11: "What's the
Point of Getting Closer?"
Episode 11   What's the Point of Getting Closer?
Humanity, preach love!
Is that what this show is about?
Clink...